Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
THE APARTMENT JOB
Then will you let me be the keeper
of your vault?
You are the perfect man
to take on that position.
MR. SON. SEOUL POLICE CHIEF
Yes?
Hey. Mr. Park.
Did you know
Park Yong-man was terminally ill?
What did you just say?
They say it's pancreatic cancer.
He has about three months left.
You'd better hurry
if you don't want him to die in there.
Get the ten billion.
I'm bringing over the ten billion.
so release him.
Right now!
Uncle Hae-kang. here's a gift.
This is amazing.
You could be an artist. Gyeong-buk.
Is it really okay for me to have this?
You're the head of our family. Uncle.
It seems like President Seo was taken out.
His entire family disappeared as well.
Then what did you see after failing?
This is my family.
We're a very happy family.
Gyeong-buk!
Wow!
People.
The people who are protecting me.
and the people I should protect.
You crazy bastard. Are you kidding me?
You said you'd bring the money.
You were bringing the ten billion!
That's why I had him moved
to the hospital at this late hour.
Do you think I'm playing around?
All right. You just watch.
You're the one
who's killing Park Yong-man.
Understand? You jerk.
What the hell are you doing? Let go of me.
The medical bail comes first.
I told you. our deal comes first!
The situation's changed.
As you know.
he doesn't have much time left.
That's why you'd better bring the money.
Bring me the ten billion. you asshole!
Let go of me.
You'd better hurry.
because that ten billion you want
is on borrowed time too.
Understand?
PATIENT PARK YONG-MAN
Yong-man.
Hang in there.
Hang in there just a while longer.
Just a little more.
GUNAM TAESAN FACILITY MANAGER
They received the money.
He needed the ten billion won
for his old boss.
but he didn't take my money?
Don't you think he has the potential
to be my vault keeper?
I've been meaning to ask…
Why Park Hae-kang?
Stupid dogs only care about food.
But once a smart dog is trained.
it stays loyal to its owner.
He planted relics
to stop the new town construction
and doubled the reserve fund fee.
Park Hae-kang
can see the bigger picture.
I heard you delivered the money safely.
Thank you so much.
But what brings you here at this hour?
I remembered
that we haven't discussed
a very important matter.
What exactly…
You've acquired someone more capable
than President Seo.
so you should
compensate me accordingly.
We haven't discussed your payment.
I'm not a cheap guy.
We almost had a serious misunderstanding.
Mr. Park.
How much do you want?
Ten billion.
I want ten billion won.
I've already doubled the reserve fund fee.
So about 600 million
will be added to the fund each month.
I believe
I'm worth at least ten billion.
Okay. fine. Ten billion.
THE APARTMENT JOB
Gyeong-nam. Je-gil. Big Guy.
Guys.
What?
Guys!
Come on.
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
How many candles is that?
-One. two. three…
-He's an old man now.
That was a success.
-Were you surprised?
-He was surprised.
Did you cry?
No. I didn't cry.
Never.
They're the people
you want to protect. aren't they?
Everyone's been saying that this place
has an amazing sauna.
Is it your first time here?
Of course.
I don't even live here.
Then how do we get in?
My friend lives here.
I can just use her card.
They don't even check your ID here.
Come on.
Unbelievable.
So we've been paying the fees
while other people used our facilities.
You saw the reserve fund fee. right?
It's doubled now.
But doesn't it seem like the elevators
are working fine now?
It does seem so.
But they should still be replaced
before any accidents occur.
Ridiculous.
Whose is this? Let me have a sip.
I can't believe it.
Hey. did you know that there are people
using our community sauna for free?
But we have to use our cards to enter.
Yes.
But some were just entering
right after someone used their card
to open the gate.
And some are secretly lending them
to other people.
I just heard there are rumors
that our sauna is good.
My goodness.
Then they're using our sauna for free?
No way. It's not even that expensive.
I just saw some people entering like that.
If that's true.
this needs to be made public.
REPORTING FACILITY MISUSE
Please. eat.
You probably had dinner.
so I prepared some light snacks.
We should make a toast.
but the guest of honor isn't here yet.
Please wait a moment.
Is someone else coming?
He's here.
Say hello.
Today's guest of honor. Park Hae-kang.
You're here today
thanks to Mr. Park.
Say hello.
Please. sit.
Sit down.
Go on.
So these two
really were working for Lee Chung-won.
When President Seo was alive.
I never got to prepare
a gathering like this.
Just how much influence does he have?
But we're a family now.
So let's all line our pockets together.
I'm joking.
Why aren't you laughing?
I'm just giving these out to you
because I'm in a good mood today.
Hand them out.
I gave you all an equal amount.
See?
Receiving gifts lightens the mood.
doesn't it?
All right. How about a toast?
Raise your glasses.
Cheers.
I…
You should have at least
told us in advance.
It hasn't been long.
What about you two?
Ever since we started working here…
Mr. Choi.
Then I'll look forward
to working with you. sir.
Were you faking a family to do this?
What?
Ha-jeong. what are you doing?
I'm coming.
You should stop this right now.
When did Mr. Lee
get Park Hae-kang on his side too?
Whatever.
It's not easy for people like us
to earn money.
You know very well
how much education costs. don't you?
Yes.
All I want
is to live quietly without any trouble
until my kid graduates
from school in Canada.
So please cooperate. Ha-jeong.
Okay.
I'll get going now. Mr. Choi.
Right. Bye.
Kang Ha-ri.
Quit that stand-in gig. right now.
What?
Do you even know what you've been doing?
Do you know what kind of man
Park Hae-kang is?
What about him? What's this about?
You really are clueless. aren't you?
What's gotten into her?
Are you drunk?
TRANSACTION LEDGER
TRANSFERRED TO PRESIDENT SEO
-Is it airtight?
-Yes.
No one can tell by looking at the ledger.
Of course. I know how skilled you are.
Your sister's tuition is due soon. right?
President Seo is very attentive.
TRUE VALUE STATE
EXPENSE HISTORY
FENCE REPAIRS
(MATERIAL COSTS OVERSTATED)
LEAK REPAIRS
(CHARGED EXTRA)
How did things end up like this?
Attention. everyone.
We're all getting the same thing.
Rotisserie chicken. 15 centimeters.
grain bread with American cheese.
heated in the oven.
and leave out the pickles.
Low-sugar onion and barbecue sauce.
One. two. three. four. five…
Six of them. please.
-There are five of us. Why six?
-Yeah. why?
It's tasty. so I'm getting two.
Then one more for me.
Me too. For Gyeong-buk.
Me too.
I need to send some to my family.
so five more.
With all the ingredients.
Fifteen. then.
Fifteen?
What? You met with the two of them?
That's nerve-racking.
Inviting you all together
to skim the fund…
He really is something. isn't he?
But the thing is… Come closer.
The accounting manager
knows that we're a fake family.
How does she know?
I'll get rid of her after I finish these.
I'll hold back.
She has a dirty secret too.
so she won't be able to tell people
that we're a fake family.
Ms. Jang. and now the accounting manager…
Everyone will find out at this rate.
We'll leave as soon as I get
the ten billion from him.
-Yes. Boss.
-Let's eat.
Mr. Choi. you should see this.
What is it this time?
A complaint about people
using our facilities.
REPORTING FACILITY MISUSE
"Let's find out who they are
and shame them"?
"Freeloaders." "Free sauna."
"Security is too lax"?
They're proposing
a facial recognition system.
Why is this leading to talk
about a facial recognition system?
-No.
Why would we spend needless money
just because
of a few irresponsible people?
I'm against this.
I think so as well.
but more and more people
are agreeing to the idea.
They want to use the reserve fund?
-Yes.
-No…
I mean…
All we have to do is find the people
who are misusing our facilities
and give them a warning.
Yes. that will be enough.
Let's find them and expose them.
If rumors spread about them.
they'll be too ashamed to do it again.
But how would we find them?
All right. Good.
Stop. Right there.
The one with the pink basket.
The elderly woman in the back.
It's 12:54 and 7 seconds.
…fifty-four and seven seconds.
Check.
It's Building 303. Unit 504.
-Building 303…
-Unit 504.
Unit 504. Okay. next.
Still nothing from President Park?
No. nothing.
What about his brother?
-Goodness!
-After drinking all that tea.
he just ignores us?
We even took his side
with the fee increase proposal.
Right?
This isn't right.
I didn't think he'd be like this.
Things were better with President Seo.
It was nice being a building rep.
We have to pay for heating bills now.
And we're not getting any kickbacks.
This is no fun.
Do we have to keep working
as building reps like this?
What choice do we have?
It's not like we can
bring Park Hae-kang down.
Isn't there some clever way
to bring Park Hae-kang down?
Things have been noisy lately
about stopping unauthorized use
of our facilities.
Unauthorized use?
Then let's at least go and sit
in the management office. not here.
Good idea.
Let's hang around there instead.
I'm sure we'll find something.
-Let's go.
-Really?
-Get up.
-Okay.
-Hello.
Hi. Yun-seo.
Hello.
Is something wrong?
We just wanted to chat
with the residents a bit.
And since you're all working so hard.
-we want to hear about your troubles.
-Right.
We want to chat over some tea.
I see.
But Mr. Choi and President Park
just went to check the security footage.
Don't mind us. You can keep working.
We have lots of time on our hands.
-I'll make the coffee myself.
-Sure.
But where are all the other employees?
Everyone's busy.
Yes?
No one's there?
Hang on.
Building 105. Unit 702.
It's a rental unit.
Looks like
only elderly residents live there.
Why don't you check in the afternoon?
Okay.
Building 105?
That's where I live. What's going on?
We're visiting residents
who misused the community facilities
and giving them a warning.
But they're not at home.
I guess rental units
are misusing the facilities.
They shouldn't do that
when they're living here for free.
Pardon?
No. it's not that--
You seem busy. We'll come back next time.
Right.
I'll make my own coffee.
-Bye.
Bye…
What is it?
I think I got it.
-What?
-Got what?
A way…
to drag Park Hae-kang down.
What is it?
MOST FACILITY MISUSE
COMES FROM RENTAL UNITS…
"Rental units should be limited
from using community facilities."
"Rental unit beggars are the worst."
"I'm struggling to pay
my mortgage interest."
"It's infuriating how people
in the rental units have it so easy."
"Reveal the rental units."
What kind of nonsense is this?
What a load of crap.
I'm sorry. sir.
I was just asked
who lives in Building 105. Unit 702
because they weren't answering their door.
so I said it was a rental unit.
But the building reps who came
overheard me.
I don't know why this led
to all the talk about the rental units.
It's not something to apologize to me for.
But you should apologize directly to them.
They're moving out.
CAN'T YOU EVEN PAY FOR A SAUNA?
This is a social mix apartment complex.
The rental units and owner-occupied units
are mixed here.
so the residents
couldn't know which units were rented.
But the residents acted as though
they had been waiting for this to happen.
so they seemed quite shocked.
They said they just wanted
to brag to their old neighbors
about living in a nice apartment complex.
And here.
They asked that this be used
for the apartment complex.
And they apologized
for causing a commotion.
It's the sauna fee.
Here.
Try another color too.
Next color…
Good.
You're so smart.
Draw one at the bottom.
Wow. that's so cool.
That's amazing.
So cute.
Who is this?
-That's a nice rainbow.
-Is this Mom?
What on earth are you doing right now?
They're water-soluble crayons.
It'll get washed away in the rain.
This is still a public place.
Are you seriously drawing
on a public building?
We weren't…
Oh gosh.
Why do people here
have no sense of responsibility?
Are you teaching your kids that it's okay
to vandalize public property?
We just told you
that it'll get washed away in the rain.
Look.
There's no forecast of rain
for a whole week.
Then we can just spray water on it.
And you can talk quietly.
Why are you shouting
when there are kids here?
So I guess you do feel embarrassed
getting called out in front of them.
It's okay for kids to scribble sometimes.
and we said we'd erase it.
You said the rain would wash it away.
That means you had no intention
of erasing it before it rained.
You should be the ones
stopping your kids from doing that.
but you're doing it with them?
Are you thoughtless or ill-mannered?
Or just uneducated?
You're unbelievable!
-Did you hear that?
-Ma'am.
You're being…
What?
Am I wrong?
You young mothers
should have some sense of ownership!
Is this really that big of a deal?
We all have a sense of ownership!
We own our units!
I'm an owner too!
Right. Good for you.
If you took out massive loans
to become owners
of apartments like this.
you should be thinking
about educating your kids
and helping raise the property value.
If rumors spread
about how bratty the kids are here.
the prices will drop!
-Hey!
What? Why?
-Gosh.
-My goodness.
What's with that woman?
As if she doesn't have any loans.
Isn't there a way to find out?
Is there?
We can check the property registry.
Anyone can view it
if you know the address.
Really?
She's in Building 112. right?
Yes. Unit 902.
We don't need to go that far.
It's true that we drew
on a public building.
We know it was our fault.
but she was going on
about a sense of ownership
and calling our kids brats
over something so trivial.
We didn't need to hear
such harsh comments.
You're right.
She speaks so harshly.
-She was spewing nonsense.
-Yeah.
Let's sleep early today. okay?
Mom. what's a loan?
Well…
It's when you borrow money from a bank
when you don't have enough.
Do we not have money?
What?
That lady earlier
said we had a huge loan.
No. well…
It's not huge.
We have a bit.
Just a little.
Hardly anyone buys an apartment
without a loan.
She spoke as if she didn't.
Should I check?
What unit was she in again?
Building 112. Unit 902…
PROPERTY REGISTRY
Oh my gosh.
You have to do well today. okay?
That sapling incident and the drawings…
Remember everything she put us through.
Too many to count.
It's just ridiculous.
Make sure she won't even dare
to say a thing.
-Okay?
-Take her down a peg.
You can do it.
-We're relying on you.
-You can do it.
TRUE VALUE STATE
RESIDENTS' ASSOCIATION MEETING
Let us begin
the residents' association meeting.
Today's agenda
is how to prevent misuse
of the community center.
Excuse me.
Before starting the meeting.
there's something I thought
you should know in advance.
Let me announce something.
For the past month.
President Park and I have been staying up
all night reviewing security footage.
checking the residents who have been
misusing the community center.
We've identified a total of 108 cases.
Four of them were from rental units.
and the remaining 104
were from purchased units.
-Purchased units?
-What?
That's way more than the rental units.
The rental units
must have been pretty frustrated.
Which purchased units
were being so thoughtless?
Hang on.
Are you sure about this?
We visited each household to confirm this.
and they apologized.
They promised not to do it again.
So everyone.
stop attacking the rental unit residents.
and let us all get along--
But. Ms. Jang.
aren't you taking the rental units' side
because you're one too?
-Rental unit?
-Ma'am.
Everyone here lives
in an owner-occupied unit.
Our management rules state
that only those in owned units
are able to participate
in the residents' association meetings.
Then Ms. Jang should clearly leave.
Because she doesn't own her unit.
It's a rental unit
managed by the government.
She always acted
like she had a say in everything.
She spoke like that
when she's in a rental unit?
-Wow.
-No wonder.
She was always yelling at our kids.
You were investigating stuff
and pretending to be a homeowner
when you didn't have the authority?
Hey.
Pretending?
That means she's been violating
our management rules.
Residents from rental units
don't have the right to be here. so leave.
She's right. Leave.
Go.
Get out!
Hurry up and leave!
Why?
Why wouldn't I have the right?
The government gave me the right
to live here as if it were my own home
for 30 years without worrying.
I don't pay as much as you.
but I'm not living here for free.
I pay the maintenance fees. the rent.
and the government
pays for the reserve fund.
I'm paying to live here too.
Why shouldn't I have the right?
I don't own my house.
but I lived with a bigger sense
of ownership than any of you.
It wasn't just my own house.
I cleaned all around
the apartment complex.
treating it as my own home.
Was anyone here more invested
in True Value's affairs than I was?
Anyone?
Building reps. say something.
You have the title.
but did any of you even care
if any electricity was being wasted
or if any facilities were broken.
causing danger to the residents?
Did any of you even care
about things like that?
Even so.
you're still from a rental unit.
Do I need some kind of qualification
to want to make
the apartment complex I live in
a better place?
Just because
I'm a tiny bit poorer than you.
am I supposed to shut up
and keep my head down?
Management rules?
What kind of stupid management rules
are like that?
How…
How could you treat people like that?
Oh. whatever.
It's still against the rules.
It's clearly stated.
-This is wrong.
-We should follow procedure.
-We should stick to…
-Stop.
Sir! Be careful!
Be careful not to scratch anything.
-To the right.
-This way.
Don't put it there.
You have to place them on the mat.
Don't put them on the floor.
You moved to a nice place. ma'am.
It's a new apartment.
No need for such formality.
I really
don't need to worry about a house anymore!
This will be my home for 30 years.
So I guess I can call myself the owner.
I'll be relying on you. elevator.
Did you have to bring that up
in front of everyone?
It just seemed
like you wanted to humiliate her.
Was that your intention?
I was rash.
I'm sorry.
You should be apologizing
to Ms. Jang. not me.
I really can't believe that Ms. Jang
is in a rental unit.
You should've checked when she applied
as a building rep candidate.
You really didn't know. Mr. Choi?
I didn't.
She was meddling in everything.
so of course I thought she owned her unit.
Who would've imagined
it was a rental unit?
She stuck her nose into everything.
Sang-tae. don't talk about her like that.
How can you say that
after hearing everything she said?
I was just…
Ms. Jang even went around
scraping gum off the ground.
Yeah.
Ms. Jang loves and cares for True Value
more than any of the owners.
Mom.
I might get a scholarship this semester.
Okay.
Mom.
Even if we don't own this house.
I've been really happy living here.
So I wondered why I was so happy.
and it was because of you. not this house.
Because you're happy.
Mom.
The house isn't what's important.
What matters is the happiness
of the people living there.
I'm going to school now.
This place is good.
I'm sure you didn't call me
just to enjoy a nice meal.
Why did you want to see me?
Well. it's about
the Oman New Town project.
We need to add more rental units
than we originally planned.
-Why?
-Isn't it obvious?
The VIP is pursuing policies
for ordinary people.
so he wants to show off
about adding more rental units
in the new town.
Increasing housing supply
while supporting vulnerable groups…
It creates a good image.
Did they replace the head chef?
Why does it feel like I'm chewing on sand?
Are you enjoying the food?
You have quite the stomach.
enjoying it
after the bomb you threw at me.
Have a drink.
An apartment costs a fortune.
and they want them for free?
The government
is basically extorting money from me.
Are they thugs or what?
Damn rental units…
I want to get rid of them all.
TRUE VALUE FACILITY MANAGER
What is it?
You told me to report to you
every two days.
Go on.
It's been kind of noisy here
with conflict between the rental units
and owned units
surrounding the misuse
of community facilities.
President Park is probably getting
quite a headache because of this.
Rental units always seem
to be the problem.
Give me back my apartments. you thieves!
Are you thugs or what?
Why did you call me at this hour?
Drink this. It's good for your health.
I heard you're having trouble
with the rental units.
I'm pretty irritated because of them too.
It's not really them.
but the way people view them.
Whatever the case.
the rental units are the problem.
The government
wants my apartments for free.
I gave them some. but they want more.
They act as if they own them.
They want to steal mine
and give them out as rental units.
so it's only natural
for the owner to be pissed.
The conflict between
the owned units and rental units…
Right. Conflict.
Should we just start a war between them?
There's nothing more entertaining
than watching a fight.
"Social mix." That's exactly the kind
of policy dreamed up by bureaucrats.
People from different social classes
living together?
Isn't that some kind of pipe dream?
Let's be honest.
Why don't we just mark the rental units
with signs on their doors?
You need to know
who your opponents are to fight them.
Right?
Never mind.
There's no need for the staff
to do so much work.
Just…
reveal all the rental units. Mr. Park.
I'm preparing the ten billion
that I promised you.
But I need some time
to gather that much cash.
If you reveal all the rental units.
I could get it prepared faster.
Did you add eggs?
Eggs are expensive.
There's only enough for Gyeong-buk.
Hey. what about me?
Elderly people need protein as well.
I'll eat them then.
Sure. I need carbs too.
-You're back.
-Yes.
Ms. Kang. you're still here.
I'm going now.
She must have been waiting for him.
She must've missed him all day.
You know I can hear you. I'm leaving now.
Bye.
Get home safely.
Did you eat. Boss?
MANAGEMENT REGULATIONS
Ms. Kang. can you work overtime today?
"Overtime."
I can't believe that sounds so sweet.
I think my heart is working overtime.
This is the Special Act
on Private Rental Housing.
Paragraph 2 states you can form
a council of lessees' representatives.
But this regulation book
was made by the developer
when the residents first moved in.
and it's never been revised.
But I don't understand this part.
This part in the regulations.
What about this?
A love story…
Big Guy. what are you doing?
Should we get them some snacks?
It's not the time for that.
We should give them some privacy.
Close the door.
What are they doing?
-Do you need anything?
-Sorry!
Are you okay?
Aren't you bleeding?
So…
Get out!
Forgot this.
Seriously…
What brings you here?
I have something to tell you.
Sure.
Ms. Jang.
I need you to quit.
You too?
Quit your role as Senior Secretary.
How about managing
apartment affairs with me
as another president?
So with the revision
to the rental housing laws.
tenants in rental housing complexes
with 150 or more units
should have formed
a tenants' representative council.
That's right.
But there are 1.200 rental units here.
Why hasn't one been formed?
We can make one now.
We're going to form
a tenants' representative council.
There's a tenants' representative council?
True Value's regulations don't state
anything about a tenants' council.
I'll correct any wrong
management regulations here.
According to the Special Act
on Public Housing
and the Special Act
on Private Rental Housing.
rental housing residents may also form
a representative council.
Why don't you step up for this?
Me?
From now on.
make your voice heard
as a representative of the tenants.
President Park…
TENANTS' COUNCIL
BUILDING REPRESENTATIVE ELECTION
Mr. Park. you're smarter than I thought.
It's all thanks to our overtime work.
Don't forget my overtime pay.
CANDIDATE PROFILE
Jang Suk-jin can do a great job
I'm running for tenants' representative.
We're holding an election. Please read it.
I'm Jang Suk-jin.
Candidate 1. Jang Suk-jin.
-I'm a candidate.
-A tenants' rep?
We need tenants' representatives
to improve the apartment.
DON'T IGNORE THE RIGHTS
OF 1.200 HOUSEHOLDS
Hello. please take a look.
We're electing tenants' reps.
Candidate 1. Jang Suk-jin.
You may begin.
Hello.
I'm Candidate 1
for building representative
on the tenants' council. Jang Suk-jin.
I live in a rental unit.
I can't believe I got selected.
I'm enjoying the comfort
and happiness of True Value
for a small amount of money.
Hello.
It's a rental unit
managed by the government.
I understand the sense of superiority
that some homeowners have.
You've worked extremely hard.
mortgaged your futures.
and sacrificed other chances at happiness
to buy your apartments.
However. I would like to ask you
to acknowledge the residents
in rental units
as a part of True Value's community.
We do not wish to live here
as shameful parasites
living off True Value.
I would like to live here proudly
as a resident of a rental unit.
enjoying my freedom
and fulfilling my responsibilities.
Anyone here?
Light's still on.
I will take on the responsibility
of caring for and protecting
the facilities of this community
as if they were my own.
Here.
I. Jang Suk-jin.
will represent the tenants
and do my best to cooperate
with the homeowners
to create a better environment
at True Value.
Thank you.
I TOTALLY AGREE WITH YOU…
I HOPE YOU GET ELECTED!
"I support you."
"Thank you."
I'm so grateful.
PRESIDENT JANG SUK-JIN
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR APPOINTMENT!
-Congratulations.
Thank you!
Thank you. everyone!
Here's your certificate.
"President Jang Suk-jin."
"You are hereby appointed president
of the tenants' representative council."
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I got a certificate!
I look forward to working with you.
President Park!
I'll keep doing my best
to love True Value State!
You can love True Value a little less.
No. I love True Value so much.
Look at this. everyone.
Mothers. Oh my gosh.
Hang on.
Congratulations. President Jang.
I'm really sorry about before.
It's fine. I've already put it behind me.
Let's work together from now on.
President Jang!
How about a photo together?
-Gather round.
-Let's take one.
Come here.
All right. Oh gosh!
What?
President Park.
-President Park. you should come here.
-Sorry.
All right. then.
Say "Suk-jin" on the count of three.
Mr. Choi!
One. two. three.
-Suk-jin!
TENANTS' COUNCIL
PRESIDENT JANG SUK-JIN
Walking around our apartment complex
as a president
feels so different.
Damn it.
They always throw trash
in places like this.
Geez.
Ms. Jang. you're a president now.
Maybe you should watch your language…
Oh. you're right.
You're absolutely right.
I should be more cautious now.
But President Park.
I don't care
who you used to be
or what you did in the past anymore.
What?
It doesn't matter
what your intentions were
when you created a fake family
and became the president.
I feel like
you were sent from the heavens
to make this place
a better apartment complex for us.
Isn't that enough?
Where have you been all this time?
Oh gosh. Choco's owner.
He's not cleaning up after his dog again.
He did that last time too.
Choco!
Hey!
You should clean up after your dog!
A better place…
ELECTION RESULTS
VERIFYING MY RENTAL UNIT
I told him to reveal the rental units.
and this is what he does?
They're revealing themselves voluntarily.
Does this make any sense?
Is this
Park Hae-kang's magic?
This is entertaining…
but I feel strangely uncomfortable.
I'm home.
I guess she's still working.
What a mess.
What?
Darn it. Ha-jeong's going
to nag me about this.
I always mess up
when I do something I usually don't do.
What is this?
TRANSACTION LEDGER
PARKING GARAGE LIGHT INSPECTION
(NOT CONDUCTED)
WALKWAY CRACK REPAIRS
(REDUCED SCOPE)
EXTERIOR WALL CRACK INSPECTION
(NOT CONDUCTED)
LANDSCAPE PLANTING REPAIRS
(FALSIFIED QUANTITIES)
You…
How did you…
Is this what you were doing
in the management office?
What the hell have you been doing?
It's nothing.
You don't need to know.
It's not nothing.
You supported me
with money you earned like this?
With filthy money?
What's filthy about money?
There's no such thing as filthy money.
Money is just money.
Kang Ha-jeong.
What else could I have done. then?
How could I pay for law school tuition
with my salary?
You said you earned a lot.
You said you had a good salary!
So this is why you were earning a lot.
It was stupid of me to believe you!
You don't need to worry about this.
I'm handling this on my own.
Stop this. right now.
Do you even know
what you've gotten yourself into?
I just did as I was told.
and I was paid for it.
Ha-jeong!
Have you lost your mind? Kang Ha-jeong!
No…
I was the one who was crazy
for eating. sleeping.
and studying with that money.
Mr. Choi…
I'm really sorry.
but I can't do this any longer.
I'm really going to quit now.
So tell Mr. Lee for me.
Ha-jeong.
If you can't do this.
you can accept Mr. Lee's offer.
No. I don't need that.
Let's not do this.
This
could be a matter
of life and death for us.
I'm telling you. I can't do this.
I'm going to pretend I didn't hear this.
I have a ledger.
Ha-jeong.
I recorded everything we've done so far.
If…
If you let me quit.
I'll get rid of the ledger
and live quietly for the rest of my life.
Ha-jeong!
PRESIDENT LEE CHUNG-WON
I…
There's an emergency. sir.
She has a handwritten ledger?
Unbelievable.
So is she thinking of blackmailing me?
She's quite crafty. isn't she?
I really had no idea. sir.
But it doesn't seem
like she has any ill intentions.
If you just allow her to quit…
I can't just leave her be.
She said she'd live quietly if she quit.
And she's trustworthy.
You're so naive. Mr. Choi.
Pardon?
She's been preparing this meticulously
for a long time.
How can you trust someone
who's holding a huge missile in her arms?
She…
She's been
cooperative until now.
She's only asking to quit.
We can trust her.
You know…
I really hate having to wear wet shoes.
not being able to wash my hands
after using the bathroom.
not being able to shower
after working out.
things like that.
I really despise that feeling.
It makes me feel really uneasy.
But right now.
Kang Ha-jeong is making me feel that way.
I feel uneasy.
I feel so uneasy!
ACCOUNTING MANAGER
KANG HA-JEONG
Hey.
Join me.
Come on. Join me.
It's boring doing this alone. Come on.
Sure.
What do you do when you get a hangnail.
Mr. Park?
Do you tear it off. or just leave it?
I tear it off.
I knew it.
I tear it off. even if I start bleeding.
It makes me uneasy.
Can you do something for me?
What is it?
Mr. Kim will contact you later tonight.
It's nothing special.
You just need to drive.
Just get in the car
and drive when I tell you to.
and stop when I tell you to stop.
It will be easy.
And when it's over.
I'll give you the ten billion.
I'll count on you. then.
Start the engine and wait inside.
He'll call you.
This is Park Hae-kang.
Yes. I know.
Of course. I recognize your voice.
Did you start the car?
Yes.
All right.
Now accelerate gently
and head out onto the main road.
Good.
Go straight.
then turn left into the main road.
Okay. Turning left.
Good. You're a good driver.
It's almost over.
SHOULD WE HAVE SPICY RICE CAKES LATER?
Why don't you start
increasing the speed now?
There's going to be a bus stop
about 300 meters in front of you.
Do you see it?
Yes. I see it.
Crash into the woman
standing there!
Park Hae-kang…
All right.
I'm coming to you.
This is ten billion won.
I told you I'd give you the money
once you did this.
You can save your old boss
with this money.
You shouldn't leave him there
when he's already sick.
All you had to do
was crash into a woman
standing right there.
You've pulled off harder things than that.
but you fail to do the easiest job?
I may be a bad guy.
but you're just trash.
Trash?
You're being quite rude to a guy
who's interested in you.
I don't date trash.
Then what will you do with me?
I think
I can make things
very interesting for you.
THE APARTMENT JOB
I would like to suggest a safety patrol.
We should show everyone
that we're the ones
who care the most about this place.
Goodness. What is all this?
That's Gyeong-buk's kindergarten.
President Park. we need you to step up.
Of course.
I should step up as the president.
Has the building really aged this fast?
No. it's shoddy construction.
President Park's wife?
So it's you. You tried to kill my sister.
How about 500 million?
I'm sure that's more than what you got
for playing Park Hae-kang's wife.
If you want him released…
Police! Open the door.
…bring me the ledger.
Simple. isn't it?
It's not something you can handle.
Hand it over to me.
I can't hand it over.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today